ref	
http://www.englishtown.com.tw/community/channels/article.aspx?articleName=103-begbiz

"Good morning, Ms. Smith."
"What can I do for you?"
"I’m sorry, I don’t know the answer." "But I will find out."
"Would you mind looking at this report?" 或 "Could you take a look at this?

In my opinion/I'm afraid I don't agree

-------------------------------------------------------------
ref
http://www.businessweekly.com.tw/blog/article.php?id=3045
痛才是重點，因為痛才無法進行操作，手不是重點，用pain當主詞。
（X） His arms were painful, which made it difficult for him to operate the machine.
（O） The pain in his arms made it difficult for him to operate the machine.

astonish 使驚訝;
confuse 使困惑;
convince 使信服; 
fertilize 使肥沃;
involve 使捲入;
terrify 使驚恐;
impress 使獲得深刻印象;
grieve 使悲傷等。
（X） My answer to the question made him feel disappointed.
（O） My answer to the question disappointed him.
我對問題的回答讓他失望。

（X） This made me think about an old saying “Practice makes perfect."
（O） This reminded me of the old saying “Practice makes perfect."
這讓我想到熟能生巧。

（X） I have worked for the company for many years. I’d like to change my job.
（O） With so many years working for the company, I feel it’s time for a career move.
我已經在這家公司服務多年，該是轉換跑道的時候了。


-------------------------------------------------------------------------
ref
http://blog.udn.com/corecorner/6311830#ixzz2NqyfTlyS


(不好) "Your mail has been received."/"Your complaint is being looked into."
(好) "I have received your mail."/"We are looking into your complaint."

"You" 態度：You will receive your computer by next week.
"We" 態度：We are happy to have your order. We shipped it by July 21.

寫email最忌諱文縐縐，要打電話給人就用call，要去拜訪人就說visit，不要用模模糊糊的contact。

模糊：Contact, Soon
明確： call, write, visit, by March 15

(不好)冗長：
-The paper jam had the effect of a destructive force on the copy machine. (12)
-We have enclosed a brochure which shows further details of manufacture. (11)
(好) 精簡：
-The paper jam destroyed the copy machine. (5)
-The enclosed brochure shows further manufacture details. (7)


每個行業都有自己的行話，email溝通時候要確定別人懂不懂你的行話，也儘量不用華麗詞藻。西方的語言習慣，他們更願意使用簡練而樸實的語言；比如
X"We look forward to a bright and glorious future of cooperation"，就不如直接寫成
O"We hope to have the opportunity to work with you in the future."，這樣才更加符合西方人的語言習慣。

迂迴 ：
-The choice of exogenous variables in relation to multi-collinearity is contingent upon the derivations of certain multiple correlation coefficients.
直接：
-Supply determines demand.

拙：
-Obviously, if you'd read your policy carefully, you'd be able to answer these questions yourself.
-In order to complete the claim you made, simply. . .
-We want to get our check.
巧：
-I'm glad to clear up these questions for you.
-To complete your transaction, . . .
-To keep your account in the preferred customer class, send our check for NT$200,000 today.

不專業：
-How are you?
-Can we work together?
專業：
-Introduction: Our Product Offerings for Bright Ideas Imports.
-Proposal: Bright Ideas Imports-ABC‘s Partnership Opportunity.


音同
affect 影響
effect 影響/效果

音同
farther具體的遠
further抽象的遠

eg是舉例
ie = that is 

------------------------------
ref

4、Native speaker 本國人。不唸Negative speaker
Native和另一個字negative形音很像，常常聽到有人會把兩個字混在一起。
native的意思是天生的、本國人，發音是[ˋnetɪv]，
negative是否定的、消極的，發音是[ˋnɛgətɪv]，意思完全不同。

5、Economy、Economic 和economist。注意重音和意思
這幾個字重音很容易唸錯。
economic經濟的，要注意與economical的差別，
economical通常當作「節儉的」解釋。
economy則是經濟的名詞，
economics是經濟學，
economist 是經濟學家，這幾個字的讀音也要注意一下，
economy和economist的重音在第二音節(-co-)，
economics、economic、economical的重音在第三音節(-no-)，O的發音是[ɑ]。

、Cooperate和corporate不一樣
先講
co-o-pe-rate，是「合作」。注意兩個o要分開來發音，重音在第二個o，發成[koˋɑpə͵ret] ，
cooperation是它的名詞。
corporate[ˋkɔrpərɪt]，注意r要發出聲音，另外rate發成[rɪt]，在英文裡不常見，
corporate	adj.法人的，团体的，社团的； 公司的，总体国家的； 〈古〉团结的； 共同的，全体的
certificate也是一樣，唸成[sɚˋtɪfəkɪt]。



Skype [skaɪp]
app     [æp]
debt（債務）	det

Island	[ˋaɪlənd]
isle	[aɪl] 

3、coupon 折價券。[ˋkupɑn]  不唸"Q" pon 




