As 2012 draws to a close
extend 擴展
extend my sincere	致以誠摯的
loyalty 忠誠
unwavering	堅定不移
commitment 	承諾
mutual	/myou錯/	共同的
exceptional /a say p tional / 優秀
record-breaking	破紀錄
gratitude 鬼tidyou	感謝
demonstrated /佇門s醉/	證明
extraordinary /餓s卓nary/	非凡
unprecedented/un pway森dent/	史無前例


Dear SAP Partner,
As 2012 draws to a close, 
I would like to wish you a happy holiday season and extend my sincere thanks for your continued loyalty,
partnership and unwavering commitment to our mutual business and customers.

What an exceptional year 2012 has been so far! 
As we look to build on the record-breaking growth we've achieved in the first three quarters of 2012, 
I cannot express enough gratitude for your contribution. 
Together we have demonstrated /佇門s醉/that the extraordinary power and value of partnership can deliver amazing results 
for our mutual business and unprecedented success for our customers.

Today partners are at the core of SAP, and the key growth driver for the business. As of Q3 year-to-date, 
partners represented more than 34% of SAP's overall software revenue. 

Together we are accelerating business across all segments and doing what no other company can by partnering in new ways, 
and driving co-innovation with SAP platforms and solutions like SAP HANA. 
We are capitalizing on an opportunity that comes with meeting the needs of customers 
by leveraging the game changing power provided by our five market categories: 

Applications, Analytics, Mobile, Database and Technology, and Cloud.

SAP's success now transcends well beyond the company's historical presence 
as an enterprise software company serving larger enterprises
— to a leading business platform company with a firm leadership position in the SME market 
— successfully serving customers of all kinds and sizes. 
This would not be possible without you. 

In fact, partners are essential to what SAP is today 
— and even more importantly to what we want to be in the future. 

Whether it's co-innovating to deliver new solutions, 
expanding our reach to new markets and customers, 
or driving amazing value and adoption of our solutions, 
together we are doing what no one else in this industry can — helping the world run better!

This time of year tends to bring out the dreamer in all of us. 
It's when we pause to reflect on everything we've accomplished. 
But perhaps more importantly it's a time to look toward the future. 
I have to say; seeing what we have done together this year makes me a believer that great things are possible. 
I am more confident than ever that our future is bright, 
and together we will continue to prosper while helping more customers realize the value of SAP solutions.
Dream and Believe. Let's end 2012 strong and enter 2013 with more confidence than ever. 
There is no limit to what we can achieve TOGETHER!
From all of us at SAP, I wish you and your family a happy holiday season and a successful and inspiring New Year!
Thank you for partnering with SAP!

Sincerely,
Eric
Eric Duffaut
Global President and Corporate Officer
SAP Ecosystem & Channels
 

	 

  


 	Connect: 	 	 	 	 

Manage Your Profile | Copyright/Trademark | Privacy | Impressum 
SAP Global Ecosystem and Channels - 95 Morton Street | New York, NY 10014, USA
Pflichtangaben/Mandatory Disclosure Statements: http://www.sap.com/company/legal/impressum.epx 
Diese E-Mail kann Betriebs- oder Geschäftsgeheimnisse oder sonstige vertrauliche Informationen enthalten. Sollten Sie diese E-Mail irrtümlich erhalten haben, ist Ihnen eine Kenntnisnahme des Inhalts, eine Vervielfältigung oder Weitergabe der E-Mail ausdrücklich untersagt. Bitte benachrichtigen Sie uns und vernichten Sie die empfangene E-Mail. Vielen Dank.
This e-mail may contain trade secrets or privileged, undisclosed, or otherwise confidential information. If you have received this e-mail in error, you are hereby notified that any review, copying, or distribution of it is strictly prohibited. Please inform us immediately and destroy the original transmittal. Thank you for your cooperation.




